<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>false</available>
    <description>Provider affirmatively responds to initial outreach or last ditch email</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>CLO338_Response_TrialInformationList_014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Re:</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you, Dr. {!Match_Record__c.MD_Last_Name__c},

[Option 1: Response to IOE] Per your request, I have included information about the TRITON2 and TRITON3 clinical studies that target {!Match_Record__c.Patient_Initials__c}’s BRCA1/BRCA2 alteration. One of our Clinical Trial Advisor physicians will contact you via phone this week to further discuss these trials as a treatment option for {!Match_Record__c.Patient_Initials__c}. [Option 1]

[Option 2: Follow-up after phone conversation] It was great speaking with you regarding your patient {!Match_Record__c.Patient_Initials__c} ({!Match_Record__c.Patient_Age__c} yo {!Match_Record__c.Patient_Gender__c} with {!Match_Record__c.Cancer_Type_Lower_Case__c}) who was found to have a BRCA1/BRCA2 alteration. To view your patient&apos;s Guardant360 report, click here: https://portal.guardanthealth.com/r/A0141378. Further to our discussion about your patient’s Guardant360 report, you expressed an interest in exploring treatment options based on the BRCA1/BRCA2 alteration detected. [Option 2]

Since BRCA1/BRCA2 mutations are uncommon, we have partnered with Clovis Oncology and formed a business and financial relationship to help identify patients for the rucaparib study and to alert treating physicians about their treatment and trial options for patients like {!Match_Record__c.Patient_Initials__c}. Your patient may be eligible for [X NUMBER] of clinical trials as indicated on the Guardant360 report, including [BULLETED MENTION OF ADDITIONAL TRIALS]. 

TRITON2 and TRITON3: Clovis Oncology
Clovis’ trials, TRITON2 and TRITON3, involve a drug called rucaparib, an oral, small molecule inhibitor of PARP1, PARP2, and PARP3. Rucaparib is being investigated in metastatic castrate-resistant prostate cancer (mCRPC) patients with somatic and germline BRCA1 or BRCA2 alterations. Preliminary results from TRITON2 were the basis for Breakthrough Therapy designation for rucaparib, which was granted on October 2, 2018 by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) as a monotherapy treatment of adult patients with BRCA1/2-mutated mCRPC who have received at least one prior androgen receptor (AR)-directed therapy and taxane-based chemotherapy. Details of these trials can be found in the attached PDF.

The closest study site is {!Match_Record__c.Closest_Trial_Site__c} in {!Match_Record__c.Closest_Trial_Site_City__c}, {!Match_Record__c.Closest_Trial_Site_State__c}; additional study sites and financial support for patient travel and accommodations are available. 

Would you like me to connect you with {PI Full Name}, a nearby PI of the TRITON2 or TRITON3 study, via email so they may answer additional questions regarding eligibility, inclusion/criteria, etc. for the rucaparib study?

Sincerely,
{!User.Name}, {!User.Degree__c} 
{!User.Title}
Guardant Health, Inc.
On behalf of the Clinical Trial Advisors program

Guardant Health Match Key: {!Match_Record__c.Match_Key__c}


Guardant Health partners with the clinical trial sponsor to conduct patient referral activities.

This message is intended solely for the designated recipient(s). It may contain confidential or proprietary information and may be subject to attorney-client privilege or other confidentiality protections. If you are not a designated recipient you may not review, copy or distribute this message. If you have received this in error, please notify the sender by replying to this e-mail and deleting this message. Thank you. Ref: {!Match_Record__c.Id}</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
