<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>7/17/20 changed sender to Adriana. 2/20/19 Updated by AF to reflect Clinical Trials only 1/17/19 changed sender to Katrina 7/31/18 Removed Match Key 7/30/18 Added shortened Portal URL (now supported by Portal 7.1) -AF. 2/16/18 text copied from 1A1 Initial outreach for auto generated emailV1.A1  -AF</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>General_Operations_IOEAutomation_031</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your patient {!Guardant_360_Sample__c.MR_Patient_Initials__c}&apos;s genomic alteration indicates a potential targeted therapy clinical trial match</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Dr. {!Contact.LastName},

The Guardant360 test you ordered to identify circulating tumor biomarkers for your patient {!Guardant_360_Sample__c.MR_Patient_Initials__c} reported a {!Guardant_360_Sample__c.MR_Qualifying_Target_Alterations__c} alteration on {!Guardant_360_Sample__c.Final_Report_Date__c}. We found that this rare alteration could qualify your patient for a curated list of clinical trials.

If you would like to receive more information, please reply to this email.

To view your Guardant360 report in our secure online portal, click here: {!Guardant_360_Sample__c.Portal_Link_for_MD__c}.

Sincerely,  

Adriana Olar, MD  
Clinical Trial Advisor  
Guardant Health, Inc.  
On behalf of the Clinical Trial Advisors program

This message is intended solely for the designated recipient(s). It may contain confidential or proprietary information and may be subject to attorney-client privilege or other confidentiality protections. If you are not a designated recipient you may not review, copy or distribute this message. If you have received this in error, please notify the sender by replying to this e-mail and deleting this message. Thank you.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
